Guide to the Jim Fouratt Papers
Fouratt (Jim) Papers
- T-shirts, 1977 1990; Series VII; 83.33 Linear Feet; (50 boxes)
  - No Apologies! - May 21st 1979 San Francisco, circa 1979 (Box 194)
    Shirt commemorates the "White Night Riots".
  - General Mao in hat, undated (Box 195)
  - The Pop Group - We are all prostitutes, 1980 (Box 196)
  - The B-52's, circa 1980 (Box 197)
  - Danceteria - We serve the best music. Live-Recorded-Hot!, 1980 1989 (Box 198)
  - Danceteria - We serve the best music. Live-Recorded-Hot!, 1980 1989 (Box 199)
  - Homemade t-shirt for the band Hot Lunch, 1977 (Box 200)
  - Black Uhuru - Red, circa 1981 (Box 201)
  - Coyote - Hoboken NJ 07030, 1980 1989 (Box 202)
  - Action = Life/Silence = Death - ACT UP, 1990 1999 (Box 203)
  - Thanks Jim - Lolita Pop, undated (Box 204)
- Realia, 1980 2009; Series VIII; 3.17 Linear Feet; (3 boxes)
  Realia consists of concert passes, stickers, a Keith Haring puzzle, a stamp, drink tokens, and other objects collected by Jim Fouratt.
  - Concert passes and other memorabilia, 1980 2009 (Box 205)
  - Objects and ephemera, 1980 1999 (Box 206)
    Includes Studio 54 stickers, a Keith Haring puzzle, x-rays, penguin stamp used in Average Normal materials, and other objects.
  - Broken buttons, drink tokens, costume jewelry, and other materials, 1980 1989 (Box 207)